我去拿克里斯汀的雨靴  她今天用得上
I'll get Christine's boots. She's gonna need 'em today.
我觉得她需要艘船
I think she needs a boat.
或者是艘方舟
Or perhaps an ark.
-主意不错  骨头  -谢了
- Huh! Hey, that's a good one, Bones. - Thank you.
这是根据诺亚的神话和
It was in reference to the myth of Noah and...
-我明白  方舟  -诺亚方舟
- I got it. Ark. Yes. - ...the Ark.
尽管这神话并没经过深思熟虑
Although that myth isn't really thought out.
-为什么  -每种物种里挑两个
- Why's that? - Two of each species?
他的船上应该得包括
He would've had to include
那些让生命在水下成为可能的
submicroscopic organisms
亚微观生物们
that make life possible underwater.
这是什么
Whoa. What's this?
这是在克里斯汀的批准条里发现的
It was in, uh, Christine's permission slips.
我还在想它到哪里去了呢
Oh. Huh, I wondered where that went.
是什么意思
What do you mean, "Oh"?
这可是张七万五的支票
It's a check for $75,000.
不是什么你放错地方的小东西
That's not just something you misplace.
这是我上本书纸质版销售的预付款
It's an advance against the paperback sales of my last book.
你能在送克里斯汀去学校后
Can you deposit that at the bank
到银行兑现这支票吗
after you drop Christine off at school?
不不不  我不行
Uh, no, no, no can do.
因为这是在你名下的
Because you know what? It's in your name.
告诉过你我们该开个联名账户的
Told you we should get a joint account.
我马上把它背书转给你
I'll endorse it over to you.
不  我不能拿
No, I can't take that.
这比我一年挣的还多呢
That's more than I make in a year.
怎么了啊  布斯
What's your problem, Booth?
我们已经结婚了
We're married now.
分享一切不是婚姻的一部分吗
Sharing everything is part of that, isn't it?
没错  可我
Yeah, but I...
我得回实验室了
I need to get back to the lab.
希望是谋杀
Hopefully, this is murder,
我们待会见
and I will see you soon.
我正在网上浏览梦想中的房子
So I was online looking at dream houses,
这让我想到要再加一个房间
which got me thinking about adding an extra room.
而且你想要个画室
And you want a studio.
也能扩大成一个养虫间
Which could double as a bug room.
听着  我保证我们会在
Listen, I promise we will do it...
我找到一个可以抢的银行后做这件事
as soon as I find a suitable bank to rob.
我们能组成一个不错的抢银行小队
You know, we'd make a pretty good team.
你能开逃跑用的车
You could drive the getaway car.
不好意思  是哈金斯博士吗
Excuse me, Dr. Hodgins?
什么事
Yes?
我是罗兹伦博士
I'm Dr. Rozran.
你好
Okay.
我是桑德伍德之家的
From the Sandalwood Home.
不好意思  这是我的妻子安琪拉
Ah. Sorry. This is my wife, Angela.
桑德伍德之家是什么地方
Hi. What's the... the Sandalwood Home?
我们是一所心理健康住院治疗机构
We're an in-patient mental health facility.
由于哈金斯博士是坎特里尔集团
And since Dr. Hodgins is the sole survivor
唯一在世的继承者
from the Cantilever Group...
我明白了  我很抱歉  罗兹伦博士
I get it. I'm sorry, Dr. Rozran.
我确信您过去已收到了慷慨的捐款
I'm sure that you've received generous donations in the past,
但是坎特里尔集团已不再存在了
but, you see, the Cantilever Group doesn't exist anymore.
我来不是为了谈捐款的
I'm not here about a donation.
我是为了你的兄弟而来
I'm here about your brother.
因为基金已经超过一年没付他的费用了
Since the fund hasn't paid his expenses for over a year...
抱歉你搞错了  我没有兄弟
I'm so sorry. You made a mistake. I don't have a brother.
你是杰克·哈金斯博士  对吧
You're Dr. Jack Hodgins, right?
乔纳森和安妮哈金斯的儿子
Son of Jonathan and Anne Hodgins?
是的  但是哈金斯是独子
Yeah, but Hodgins is an only child.
这是板上钉钉的事实
That's not something you get wrong.
这样  因为杰弗里在我到桑德伍德之前
Oh. Uh, since Jeffrey has been at Sandalwood
就在那里了
since before I got there,
我认为可能是文件出了问题
I suppose it's possible the paperwork is askew.
小心  看着点身后
Heads up! Watch your back!
过来
Coming through!
好  就放在这里
Okay, right here.
这样所有人都能靠近它
That will give everyone access.
真不好意思这里一团乱  罗兹伦博士
Well, uh, sorry for the mix-up there, Dr. Rozran,
但我们不得不离开了
but we really do need to get going.
好的  我明白
Uh, yes, I understand. Uh...
我回到办公室后就解决这事
I'll settle this when I get back to my office.
非常抱歉叨扰您了
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
一个在安蒂特姆河沙场公园的巡警
A ranger at Antietam Battlefield Park
在今晨上班时发现了这些脚
spotted the feet when she came in this morning.
这只有腿还是腿上面有具尸体
Are there just legs, or is there a body attached to them?
肯定还有更多
There's definitely more,
但是可能被用雷达透不过的东西
but it could be wrapped in something
给包裹了起来
the radar can't get past.
那我们就要开挖了
Then we'll have to excavate.
奇怪的是那人既和坎特里尔有关
It's odd that he had the Cantilever connection
还有你父母的名字
and your parents' names.
是很奇怪  但事实是
Very. But the fact is
一个人不是简简单单就能失去一个兄弟的
a person doesn't just lose a brother.
我失去了父亲
I lost my father.
没错  但你知道你有个父亲
Yes, but you knew you had one.
不好意思
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
费什先生  你迟到了
You're late, Mr. Fisher.
我道歉
Apologies.
我看新闻的同时在想
I was watching the news and wondering
这是否值得我穿好衣服
if it was even worth getting dressed.
我们想你了  费什
Oh, we've missed you, Fisher.
这看上去不值得吗  费什先生
Doesn't this seem worth it, Mr. Fisher?
也许吧
It has possibilities.
右足跗骨暗示受害者是名女性
The tarsal bone on the right foot suggests the victim is female.
从右足骨骼上来看
And from the looks of it,
她的小脚趾在她死前就被卸掉了
the little toe was removed before she died.
是致死的可能原因吗
Possible cause of death?
就因为被切了小脚趾吗
By cutting off the little toe?
血友病患者
Hemophiliac?
只是说说而已
Just saying.
我想我找到了什么
Think I got something.
等等  所有人都别碰
Hold on. Nobody touch.
我曾在纽约的黑帮见过
I've seen this before in New York with gang hits.
这一定是阻碍哈金斯的雷达探测的东西
This must be what blocked Hodgins' view on the GPR.
遗骸在被埋前被泡在了碱液里
The remains were doused in lye before they were buried.
坏消息是  氢氧化钠会腐蚀遗骸
Bad news is, sodium hydroxide will eat up these remains.
更坏的消息是  这些泥和水会加速腐蚀过程
Worse news, this mud and water will speed the process.
如果骨骼受损  这可能会掩盖证据
If the bones are damaged, it could obscure evidence.
对  但好消息是
Yes, but good news,
醋可以中和碱液
vinegar neutralizes lye.
借过
Excuse me.
醋让这东西闻上去像坏掉的色拉
The vinegar is making this smell like a bad salad.
根据碱液和脱水的组织判断
Based on lye and desiccated tissue,
我觉得遗骸已被埋了一天
I'd say the remains have been buried a day,
也许是一天半前埋下的
maybe a day and a half ago.
根据露出的齿髓比
According to the exposed tooth-to-pulp ratio,
她大概25岁左右
she was in her mid-20s.
有棱角的眼窝暗示
The angular nature of the orbital socket
她是白种人
suggests she is Caucasian.
她的齿列有大量损伤
There's extensive damage to the dentition.
右侧第二  三  八上齿和下齿
Two, three, eight upper and lower teeth
已被打碎了
on the right side have been smashed.
我们不能从牙科记录找到受害人的身份
We won't get an I.D. From dentals.
碱液  牙齿被打碎了
Lye, smashing of the teeth?
某人真不想让我们找到这女人是谁啊
Somebody really didn't want us to find out who this woman was.
识骨寻踪
第九季  第十五集
识骨寻踪  第九季  第十五集
翻译  滚成一个团子  scarrrr  nikajing
翻译  紫晶藤萝  麦克杜格
时间轴  今 芝麻圆子
时间轴  旅行的木讷
校对  米苏
后期  孤帆
人人影视
YYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
总监  米苏
如果你不能把一具尸体埋得够深
Look, if you can't bury a body deep enough,
你就在上面浇满碱液让动物不把它挖出来
you cover it in lye so the animals don't dig it up.
这是经典的黑帮做法
It's classic Al Capone.
你觉得这是个黑帮成员
You think it was a mob hit?
不会吧  一个20来岁的女孩吗
Oh, geez, what, a girl in her 20s?
这是性别歧视
That's sexist.
现在一个20多岁的女孩
Nowadays a girl in her 20s can be
可以是跟小伙子一样的暴徒
just as much a mobster as a guy.
我们都想到这地步了  真是好极了
Wonderful how far we've come.
好了  听着
All right, listen.
我要你拿走这些案例
I want you to take these cases, okay?
看看里面是否有相似的犯罪
See if there's any similar crimes.
你今天真粗鲁
You're very brusque today.
-什么  -粗鲁  这是个单词
- What? - Brusque. It's a word.
好我们开始吧  霍华德·威瑟利  不是
All right, here we go. Howard Viceroy. Forget it.
犯罪手法对上了  但这人一直住在黑泽尔顿
The M.O.'s right, but the guy's in Hazelton for life.
你知道吗  你为什么不
You know what? Why don't you just
回你办公室把这些东西都过一遍
go to your office, go through all these
看看你能得到什么线索
and see what you come up with, okay?
全部这些吗
All of these?
你是个侧写师  那就去侧写
You're a profiler. So go profile.
我想你有张支票在这里
I think you got a check here.
什么  把它给我
What? Give me that.
这不是我的  这是骨头的
It's not mine. It's Bones's.
就是这让你心烦意乱吗
And that's upsetting to you?
不  这没让我心烦意乱
No, it doesn't upset me.
是有点  看到这个了没
Kind of. You see this?
这是七万五的支票啊
That's for $75,000, okay?
-骨头把它转给了我  -这礼物不错
- Bones endorsed it over to me. - It's a nice present.
这不是礼物  她让我把这存进银行
It's not a present, okay? She wants me to put it into the bank.
我们没有联名账户
We don't have a joint account.
行行好
Do me a favor.
别给我喔来喔去的
Don't give me the whole "Oh" Thing.
-你想说什么就说出来  -好
- You got something to say, just say it. - Okay.
考虑到当今社会传统男女关系的变化
With the traditional male-female dynamic changing in society,
你不情愿把你的财产和配偶合并
your reluctance to commingle your finances
暗示着这件事影响到你的男子气概
implies that it touches on issues of manhood
和你在这段关系中的地位
and your status in the relationship.
-什么  -你看  钱可以导致
- What? - Look, money can cause
两口子之间产生许多感情问题对吧
a lot of emotional issues in couples, right?
怨恨  不安全感  性功能障碍
Resentment, insecurity, impotence.
在这里打住
Hold on right there, okay?
骨头和我相处得很好
Bones and I are just fine.
在家里的每一个房间里  非常感谢你
In every room of our house, thank you very much.
但这支票还是触动了你的神经对吧
And yet that check still strikes a nerve, doesn't it?
好了  拿走这些  拿着这些文件
I tell you what. Just, here, take 'em. Take the files.
去缩小  缩小这东西
Go shrink 'em. Shrink it down.
你不能缩小文件  你只能阅读它们
You don't shrink files. You read them.
你就缩小范围
Just shrink it down.
这其中有骨折是在被埋时造成的吗
Were any of those fractures caused by the burial?
不  它们都是在濒死时造成的
No, they're all perimortem.
看上去像是在顶骨处
Looks like repeated trauma
沿着矢状缝的反复性创伤
to the parietal bone along the sagittal suture.
罪犯从不让我们失望  是不是
Criminals never disappoint, do they?
这还有其他的骨骼损伤
There are other bone injuries,
但我们在仔细检查之前需要移除其他组织
but we need the tissue removed before we can examine them.
这头上的裂伤真令人不舒服
That's a nasty crack on the head.
看上去凶手曾反复将受害人的头部
It appears the killer repeatedly smashed
撞向一个坚硬的表面
the victim's head into a hard surface.
但这看上去不像是死亡原因
But it doesn't appear to be cause of death.
我查出她是谁了
Well, I found out who she is.
残留组织提供了足够的DNA用来确定身份
The remaining tissue provided enough DNA for an I.D.
受害人是劳伦·弗兰克
The victim is Lauren Frank
来自弗吉尼亚州阿灵顿
of Arlington, Virginia.
这些是我父母的签名
These are my parents' signatures.
而且这些日期都有记录
And the dates all track.
我曾是那个家里唯一的孩子
I was the only child in that house.
我从没听人提过杰弗里这名字
I never even heard the name Jeffrey mentioned.
看上去当你母亲怀你的时候
It seems when your mother was pregnant with you,
你的父母决定如果杰弗里得到
your parents decided it would be best if Jeffrey received
全天候的照顾和监管是最好的
full-time care and supervision.
所以他们就雪藏了我的哥哥
So they warehoused my brother?
他们是从他自己手里保护他
They were protecting him from himself.
也是在保护你
And protecting you.
他有暴力倾向
He's violent?
杰弗里有分裂情感障碍
Jeffrey has schizo-affective disorder.
在他正常吃药并且接受适当治疗的时候
When he's on his meds and receiving proper treatment,
他可以自控  才智过人
he's manageable, quite intelligent
并且是个非常令人愉快的朋友
and very pleasant company.
但如果没有人照顾他呢
And when he doesn't have proper care?
他是个病人  哈金斯博士
He's ill, Dr. Hodgins,
而他的病有时候会突然发作的
and his illness can flare up.
我们不是一间监禁机构
We're not a lockdown facility.
有时候他会消失
Sometimes he disappears.
-那他怎么回来呢  -他通常会去一个
- How does he get back?  - He usually goes to one
自己熟悉的地方  所以很容易找到他
of a few places he knows, so he's not difficult to find.
但像你哥哥的情况
But with a case like your brother's,
他的看护照料费用很贵的
his care and supervision are expensive.
这就是为什么委员会让我来联系你
That's why the board had me contact you.
但我已经没什么钱了
But I don't have any money anymore.
哈金斯博士
Dr. Hodgins?
不好意思  只是...
Yeah, sorry. It's just...
我脑子一下子还没转过弯来
it's a lot to get my head around, you know?
你本来是个独子
I mean, one day, you're an only child,
结果有一天...发生了这种事
and then... all this.
我也无法设想这种事
I can only imagine.
那就是杰弗里
There's Jeffrey.
劳伦·弗兰克  二十六岁
Lauren Frank, 26 years old,
社区大学在读  父母离异
still in community college, parents divorced.
她跟父亲和继母住在一起
Lives with her father and stepmother.
她父亲是高园有限公司的总裁
You know, the dad's the CEO of Highpark, Incorporated,
某个大型软件公司
some big software company.
他的资产大约有几千万吧
He's loaded-- like, tens of millions of loaded.
她继母是个家庭主妇
Yeah, the stepmother is listed as a homemaker.
我搞不懂了  这个劳伦姑娘
I don't understand. This girl Lauren,
都二十六岁了  怎么还不搬出去住
she was 26 years old and she still hadn't moved out.
现在这种事很普遍
Yeah, it's more common than not these days.
这样的小孩被称作"啃老族"
They're called "Perma-children."
有学生贷款  高房租和低薪工作的压力
You know, between student loans, high rents, low-paying jobs,
跟父母住也显得没那么丢人了
living with your parents starts to look good.
反正劳伦是没占到什么便宜
Well, it didn't work out too well for Lauren.
他们来了
This is them, all right?
你们找到她了吗  找到劳伦了吗
Did you find her? Did you find Lauren?
对不起  这事多久...她失踪了吗
I'm sorry. How long... was she missing?
就是啊  我们这没有报案记录
Yeah, there's no report filed.
她没跟你们说吗
She didn't tell you?
你们没跟她说过话  是吧
You haven't talked to her, have you?
-没有  -我以为我们来这是为...
- No, sir.  - I thought we were here because...
不要说话  凯瑟琳  一句都别说
Don't say anything, Katherine. Not a word.
我不知道你以为我们请你们来是为什么
I don't know why you thought we brought you in.
我们根本不该来的  他们让我们别来的
We shouldn't have come. They told us not to.
老天  我们做了什么啊
Oh, God, what have we done?
她被绑架了
She was kidnapped.
我们收到了...我们收到一个快递包裹
We got a... we got a package delivered.
-凯瑟琳  -结束了  史蒂文  他们知道了
- Katherine!  - It's over, Steven. They know.
我们现在什么都做不了了
There's nothing we can do now.
不好意思  什么包裹
Sorry. The package?
我们昨天早上在家门外的台阶上
We found it outside our front doorstep
发现了一个带纸条的包裹
yesterday morning with a note.
"敢报警的话劳伦就死定了
"Call the police and Lauren dies.
照指示行动"
Instructions to follow."
里面是...
And inside...
她的脚趾
Was her toe.
如果你们没找到她  那怎么会叫我们来
If you haven't found her, why are we here?
很抱歉通知你们
We're sorry to inform you
我们今天早上发现了你们女儿的尸体
that we found your daughter's body this morning.
我们认为她是被谋杀的
We think that she was murdered.
不
No.
我们什么都照做了
We did everything.
我们在等  我们...
We were waiting, we...
我都会照做的  说什么我都答应
I would've paid, I would've paid anything.
他们为什么要这样
Why would they do this?
我简直没法相信
I can't believe this.
混账
The bastards!
是绑匪
It's the kidnapper.
他还以为自己能得到赎金呢
He still thinks he can get the money.
他不知道我们已经找到她了
He doesn't know we found her yet.
那真是大错特错
That was a big mistake.
听着  我们一定会找到你们女儿的凶手
Listen, we're gonna find out who did this to your daughter.
绑匪说他在监视我们
The kidnapper said he was watching us.
所以我们没有报警
That's why we didn't call the police.
他希望你们这么以为
That's what he wanted you to think
这样就没有人追捕他了
so no one would go after him.
你确定劳伦那天晚上没有
Are you sure that Lauren didn't go out with anyone that night,
跟什么人一起去派对之类的吗
to a party or anything like that?
确定  不然她会告诉我们并且道别的
No, she would've told us, said good-bye.
她用不着偷偷溜出去
She had no cause to sneak out.
她又不是十几岁的小孩
It's not like she was a teenager.
第二天她没有下来吃早饭
And when she didn't come down for breakfast,
我们去了她房间
we went to her room.
那时候我们才发现她不见了
That's when we'd found she was gone.
脚趾上的切口角度跟实验室里的
The angle of the incision on the toe matches the injury
跖骨末端的伤口吻合
to the distal metatarsal at the lab.
他闻到脚趾的味道了  把他弄出去
He smells the toe! Get him out of here!
奥蒂斯  过来  过来  奥蒂斯
Otis, here, here, Otis!
-怎么搞的  查克  -抱歉  史蒂文
- What the hell's going on, Chuck?  - I'm-I'm sorry, Steven.
他挣脱了  我刚准备喂他
He got out. I was about to feed him...
快把他带走
Just remove him!
证据最重要
I-I don't want the evidence compromised.
你是谁
Who are you?
查克·温特  他是这房子的管家
Chuck Winter. He's in charge of the house.
这会他的工作做得可不太好
He's not doing a particularly good job right now.
劳伦被绑架的那天晚上
Were you here the night that, uh,
-你在这里吗  -我就住这
- Lauren was kidnapped?  - I live here.
我在厨房后面有间套房
I have a suite off the kitchen.
如果有什么我能帮忙的...
If there's anything I can do...
是的  我想我们过会就会跟你谈了
Yeah, I'm sure we'll be talking to you.
你能把狗带走吗
Can you get the dog out of here?
好的  来吧
Okay. Come on.
脚趾的伤口很惨烈
The toe was removed poorly.
皮肉都扯坏了
The tissue's torn.
骨头都碎了
The bone is splintered.
-简直就是扯下来的  -老天
- It was basically ripped off.  - Oh, God!
我们还是晚点再谈这些细节吧  骨头
We can get into the details later, okay, Bones?
我想看看劳伦的房间
Well, I'd like to see Lauren's room.
我们想看看她的房间  行吗
We'd like to see her room, okay?
紧急消防梯  他们就是这样把她带走的
Emergency fire ladder-- that's how they got her out.
二楼的所有卧室都配有消防梯
All the second-floor bedrooms are equipped with them.
你觉得不止一个绑匪吗  布斯
You think that there was more than one kidnapper, Booth?
至少两个
At least two.
一个带着她  另一个稳住梯子
One to carry her and the other to steady the ladder.
你敢肯定你们什么都没动过  是吗
You're sure you haven't touched anything, right?
当然没动过
No, of course not.
没有证据表明她的脚趾是在这里被摘除的
There's no evidence that her toe was severed here.
这里没有任何血迹证据
No blood evidence at all.
也没有挣扎痕迹
No sign of a struggle,
她可能是在睡梦中被劫持的
she was probably abducted in her sleep.
门上有传感器
Now, there's sensors here on the door.
为什么门开的时候警报没响呢
Why didn't the alarms go off when they were opened?
都是我的错
It was my fault.
我跟她说空调害得她皮肤都干燥了
I told her the air conditioning was drying out her skin.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
她恨我  史蒂文  不管我做了什么
She hated me, Steven, no matter what I did.
现在我再也不能...
Oh, now I can never...
我再也不能弥补她了
I can never make it up to her.
我能带她下去吗
Can I take her downstairs?
最好是这样了
Yeah, it's probably best.
走吧
Come on.
我该回实验室去了  布斯
I should get back to the lab, Booth.
我在这没什么要做的了
There's nothing more for me here.
把这台笔记本电脑拿走吧
Take the laptop, okay?
看看安琪拉会不会有所发现  好吗
See if Angela can get anything off that, will you?
鹦鹉螺
The Nautilus.
你画的大王乌贼细节太逼真了
Hey, that's excellent detail on the Architeuthis.
你喜欢儒勒·凡尔纳吗
You like Jules Verne?
儒勒·凡尔纳吗  法国作家  科幻小说之父
他能排进我的前三
He's in my top three.
我是...
I'm...
杰克
Jack.
杰弗里
Jeffrey.
我读了凡尔纳的每一本著作
I've read everything Verne's written.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我们还在努力赶上
I mean, we're still catching up to the...
他书中的那些发明和发现
to the discoveries and inventions in his books.
小说家能能在技术出现之前
Oh, it's amazing how many novelists can see
就预见到未来的事
what the future holds
这真是令人惊叹啊
before the technologies even exist.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
爱因斯坦经常说
Einstein always said
想象力比知识更有力量
imagination is more powerful than knowledge.
是啊  他们用自己最快的速度
Yeah, well, uh, they weaponized
让爱因斯坦的多数科学发现成为武器
most of Einstein's findings as fast as they could.
他们总是说要出于善的目的
They always say they're gonna use
来利用科学  但他们从不这么做
science for good, but they never do.
说到"他们"做了什么  我就停不住了
Please do not even get me started on what "They" Do.
一切问题都会迎刃而解
All of our problems would be solved
只要放手让科学家来管理的话
if they let scientists run things.
但我立刻就被人说成是
But then, I've been told
某种阴谋论怪胎  于是...
I'm kind of a conspiracy nut, so...
这是不是表明你也能看见
Does that mean you can see, too?
看见什么
See what?
看透静电
Past the static?
他们用静电学来
They use static electricity to...
掩盖变化
to mask the changes.
这正是布拉德伯里[科幻大师]警告过我们的
It's what Bradbury warned us.
变化太细微了  你几乎很难注意到
Changes so subtle, you'd hardly even notice.
新的药品
New pills, hmm?
突然间出现了蓝色的M&M巧克力
All of a sudden there are blue M&M's?
我可能是误导你了  杰弗里  在阴谋论上
I-I-I may have misled you, Jeffrey, on the conspiracy...
不  不  不
No, no. No!
他们会利用推特这样的东西欺骗你
They will try to slip things by you like Twitter.
或是用GPS
And... GPS.
等你回过神来  你已经住在土卫六上了
And the next thing you know, you're living on Titan.
或者是海王星的某个卫星
Or one of the moons of Neptune!
这只是一个星际驿站  不是真的
See, this is just a way station; it's not real.
一切都是假的
None of this is real.
杰弗里  杰弗里  没事的
Hey, Jeffrey, hey, Jeffrey, it's okay.
这一切都是假的  不  不
None of this is real. No, no!
他们在试图...他们会利用静电
They are trying... They will use the static!
-他要看不见了  -我知道
- He won't be able to see!  - I-I-I know.
我知道  我们听到了  我们能听到
I know, I know. We hear it, we can hear it...
我要...  不  肖恩
I want... No, Sean!
-肖恩  肖恩  -是的  我是肖恩
- Sean, Sean!  - Yes, yes, it's Sean.
我在这  我在这里  听到了吗
Right here, right here. Okay?
-好  听我的  好吗  -肖恩
- All right, stay with me, okay?  - Sean.
没事了
It's okay.
我不...不知道...这是怎么回事
I don't... I don't know... I don't know what happened.
我们只是在聊天
I mean, we-we were talking.
他还挺好的  然后
He was fine, and then...
我不该说那些话的  但是...
I shouldn't have said what I said, but...
你什么都没做
You didn't do anything.
这就是我之前想跟你说明的事
This is what I was trying to explain earlier.
你父母知道这些事
This is what your parents knew.
她的电脑
Uh, her computer
被加密了  不过鉴于她装了很多
was encrypted, but since it was filled
她父亲的软件
with her father's software,
他可以给我一个运算方式
he was able to give me a work-around.
哈金斯跟他哥哥在一起吗
Hodgins is with his brother now?
是啊  就在那个地方
Yeah, at the place.
他哥哥莫名地发狂了
His brother freaked out for no reason,
那时候哈金斯刚觉得跟他在一起很轻松
just when Hodgins was feeling comfortable with him.
这件事  让哈金斯感到很难过
It just... it hit Hodgins pretty hard.
你也一定觉得很难过
It must be difficult for you, too,
因为你知道哈金斯很不好受
knowing that Hodgins is so upset.
哈金斯知道他哥哥
It's just that Hodgins feels so helpless
要被转移到政府福利院  他感觉很无助
knowing that his brother has to be moved to a state facility.
在那会得到很好的照顾的
I'm sure you'll find good care there.
但杰弗里已经在桑德伍德生活三十多年了
But Sandalwood has been Jeffrey's home for over 30 years.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
也许他需要一段时间去适应
Just a period of adjustment, I guess.
这是劳伦的提醒列表
This is Lauren's reminder list.
在绑架发生前最后一个是
The last one set to go off before the kidnapping was,
星期二  下午两点
uh, "Tuesday, 2:00 p.M.
和毛利西奥温习西班牙语
Spanish review with Mauricio."
你就是劳伦的西班牙语老师毛利西奥
So, you're Lauren's Spanish teacher Mauricio?
我只是老师的助教
I'm just the teacher's assistant.
两个穿制服带着武器的人出现在课堂上
Look, two suits with guns
直接把我带到联邦调查局了
show up at class and take me to the FBI.
你打算告诉我发生了什么事吗
Are you gonna tell me what's going on?
劳伦死了
Lauren's dead.
两晚上前她被绑架并被杀害
She was kidnapped and murdered two nights ago.
对不起  这太意外了
I-I'm sorry, this is a shock.
劳伦不止是你的学生  对吗
Lauren was more than just your student, wasn't she?
没错
Yes.
我们在约会
We're dating.
我们打算去南美洲徒步旅行
We planned a hiking tour of South America.
打算下星期就走
We planned on leaving next week.
下星期  那你肯定已经买票了吧
So, next week-- you... you must've already bought your ticket, then?
是的  怎么了
Yes. Why?
根据她笔记本上的信息
Uh, well, judging from her laptop,
劳伦是个有条不紊的人  但我们没找到
Lauren was pretty organized, but we found no plans,
为下周出行的计划和机票
no tickets booked for next week.
你们不打算一起坐飞机吗
Weren't you planning to fly together?
我用里程数换到了最后一张票
I used miles and got the last available seat.
她打算买另一班航班的
She was gonna get a ticket on another flight.
在智利会和
Meet up in Chile.
明白了
I see.
两晚前你在哪
Where were you two nights ago?
在家
I was home.
批改学期论文
Grading term papers.
好吧  在负责的探员回来之前
Okay, well, I'm gonna need you to stay here
你得待在这
until the agent in charge returns.
-为什么  -为什么
- Why? - Why?
因为你没有不在场证明却有出国的机票
'Cause you have no alibi and a ticket to leave the country.
我在说实话
I'm telling the truth!
我爱劳伦
I love Lauren.
是的  但也有可能
Yeah, but there's also the possibility
你打算带着赎金出国
that you were planning to leave the country with the ransom money.
记录显示  劳伦在1点12时
According to the log, Lauren turned off
关闭了门上的传感器
the door sensor at 1:12.
你可以发现她每晚这个时候都会这么做
And you can see she does this around the same time every night.
你没有在那之后的
You don't have any more footage
监控录像了吗
from the security cameras after that?
-没有  -这可方便绑匪了
- No. - That's pretty convenient for the kidnappers.
这些你都看过了吗  查克
And you oversee all of this, huh, Chuck?
等下
Okay, hold on.
凌晨两点  系统根据
At 2 a.M., the system rebooted
预定计划重启了
for scheduled maintenance.
通常会有30秒的运行障碍
Normally that's a 30-second interruption of service,
但是那天晚上根本就没有重新启动起来
but it never booted up that night.
史蒂文觉得那可能只是
Steven thought it was probably a bug
新软件的漏洞之类的
in the new software or something.
好吧  所以有人知道那个梯子  对吗
Right, so someone knew about the ladders, right?
而且他们还知道安全系统
And they also knew about when the security systems
会在什么时候重启
were gonna reboot.
不是每人都知道这些  对吗  查克
Not too many people with that kind of information, right, Chuck?
只有这个家的成员知道
Everybody in the family.
还有保安队和巡查
The security team, the patrol.
好的  那天晚上
Right, and you were here
你在这里的厨房吗
that night in-in your suite off the kitchen?
是的  一晚上都在
Yes, all night.
为了确保早餐准备好
And was up and made sure
-一晚都没睡  -当然了
- that breakfast was ready in the morning. - I'm sure you were.
但是因为我们认为嫌犯有两个人
But since we seem to think this was a two-man job,
希望你理解我必须要问这些问题
you understand I have to ask these questions?
当然
Sure.
检测到安全漏洞
那是谁
Who the hell is that?
-我来叫保安  -不用
- I'll call security. - Uh-uh.
我就是保安
I'm your security.
想去哪
Hey, where you going?
站住  联邦调查局
Hold on. FBI.
别紧张
Whoa, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho. Easy, hey, hey, hey, hey!
别紧张  站住
Hey, hey, hey, hey, all right, all right, easy, come on.
-别动  -别开枪  别开枪
- All right, oh-oh, right there. Okay. - Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
-你是谁  -我来领奥蒂斯
- Who are you? - I'm here for Otis.
大门的密码用不了了
Um, my code for the gate didn't work.
-他们肯定把密码改了  -你是谁
- They must've changed it. - Who are you?
我叫巴迪  来遛狗的
I'm Buddy, the dog walker.
从兽医那来的
From the vet.
看  衣服上写着呢
Look, my shirt.
这么大片地  弗兰克家怎么还需要遛狗的
Okay, with all this land, why do the Franks need a dog walker?
奥蒂斯喜欢游泳
Otis likes to swim.
我带它去海滩
You know, I take him to the beach.
我还给它梳毛  不信问劳伦
I groom him. Look, ask Lauren.
劳伦死了
Lauren's dead.
什么
What?
她死了  起来
She's dead. Get up.
你跟她有多熟悉
How well did you know her?
有时候我过来送奥蒂斯
Sometimes, when I'd drop off Otis,
我们会去她那坐下聊会天
you know, we'd sit on her deck and talk.
聊天  都聊什么
Talk? What did you talk about?
她提过有人来吗
She... she mention anybody coming around here?
她害怕谁或是陌生人吗
Was she afraid of anyone, any strangers?
没有  她基本上只是说这里的事
No, mostly she just talked about how messed up
简直一团糟
things are for her here.
怎么一团糟了
Messed up how?
只是说她很想搬出去
Well, how she wanted to move out.
她和她的继母常常吵架
How she and her stepmom fought a lot.
她还说有一次
And she said that one time
她看见她的继母和教练
she saw the stepmom and the trainer, like...
你懂的
you know.
我不懂
No, I don't.
-什么意思  -就是
- What? - Like...
-那个  -劳伦告诉你的吗
- like... - Lauren told you that?
她说这的事是一团糟
She said things were pretty messed up here.
是他们
It's them!
他们发了信息  提了条件
They sent texts with attachments.
三百万小面额  无标记的纸钞
$3 million dollars in small, unmarked bills.
下一条信息我们会发给你交易地点
Our next message will have instructions for the exchange.
你可以追踪信息是从哪发来的吗
So, you can track where the texts came from?
理论上  每个文件
Uh, theoretically. Each file,
比如发过来的劳伦的照片
like the picture of Lauren that was sent
或是绑匪发过来的语音信息
and the audio message from the kidnappers--
这些都有数码指纹
each has a digital fingerprint.
太好了
That's great.
别高兴太早  因为我还需要
Yeah, it's half great. I also need
发出信息的手机或电脑的指纹
the fingerprint of the phone or computer that sent those texts.
这些指纹会告诉我们手机的位置和主人
That fingerprint will tell us whose phone and where it is.
有问题吗
And that's a problem?
不管用的是什么手机
Whatever phone was used
都是开机发完信息就马上关机了
was turned on to send the text and then turned right off.
所以开机时间不够你用来定位
Ah, so it wasn't turned on long enough for you to trace it.
没错
Exactly.
但是应该有办法的
But there has to be a way around it.
我是说  我有一半的照片
I mean, I have half the picture.
我只需要把剩下的填进去
I just have to fill in the rest.
哈金斯
Hodgins!
很抱歉离开这么久
Hey, uh, sorry I've been away so long.
我这就回去工作
So I'm gonna get right back to work.
哈金斯  拜托
Hodgins, please.
我们不光有工作  我们还有家庭
We have our work and we have our families,
而你正经历着意料之外的事
and yours just got unexpectedly bigger, so...
如果有什么我能帮忙的
anything I can do to make things easier...
让我把没做完的粒子筛查做完
Just let me sift through the pile of particulates waiting for me.
亲爱的  你不用这么快就工作  你
Honey, you don't have to jump right back in. You can...
我们还有的案子没结呢
We have a murder to solve, so, yeah.
我只是来说一声我回来了
I just wanted to let you know that I'm back.
X射线没有检查出在豌豆骨上
There are a number of microfractures on the pisiform
有很多微裂缝
the X-rays didn't show.
这和我们在头骨后侧找到的很像
They're similar to those we found on the back of the skull.
-别处还有吗  -是的
- Did you find them anywhere else? - Uh, yes.
豌豆骨上  三角骨上
Pisiform, triquetrum
还有月状骨的两侧
and lunate-- bilaterally.
她在反复的用她的拳头打什么东西
She was repeatedly smashing her fists against something.
还有根骨的两侧
And the calcanei, bilaterally.
都是在死前造成的
All perimortem?
是的
Yes.
这些表明了她做了很大的挣扎
These all indicate quite a struggle.
她很可能试图逃跑并和绑匪对抗
She probably tried to escape and fought with her kidnappers.
不
No.
受害者自己用头部  拳头和脚跟
The victim banged her own head into the ground,
撞向地面
and fists and heels.
-什么意思  -反复地  不断地受伤
- Wait, what? - Uniform, repeated injuries.
-这些都是癫痫发作的迹象  -天呐
- They're all signs of a seizure. - Oh, my God.
你是正确的
You're right.
我还有些不习惯
Well, I feel inadequate.
你和我一起工作  费什先生
You work with me, Mr. Fisher.
我以为你已经习惯了
I'd have thought you'd be used to that by now.
我们需要找到
The question we need to answer is
是什么原因引起癫痫
what caused the seizure.
我用棉签擦拭了费什和布纳恩医生
So I... I-I swabbed the kerf marks
在尺骨上发现的切口
Fisher and Dr. Brennan found on the ulna.
它应该是一把崭新的锯
It appears to be a brand-new saw.
-那上面的油  -我不关心
- I mean, the oil on it... - I don't care.
跟切断的脚趾
Well, it's just that it's different from
上面的油不一样
whatever was used to sever the toe.
等我找到甲虫吃了什么
So after I figure out what the beetles ate...
哈金斯  别说了
Hodgins, stop. Stop.
跟我说说吧
Just talk to me.
我也想  安琪
I want to, Angie.
我只是不知道该如何开口
It's just... I-I don't know how.
只有我一个人
It was just me.
一直都只有我一个人  而现在
It was always just me, and now...
好的  好的
Okay. Okay.
那就慢慢适应
So just let that sink in.
别把我拒之门外
And please don't shut me out.
这是我们两个人的事
This is... this is happening to both of us.
他的眼睛和我妈的一样
He has my mom's eyes.
而且他也喜欢儒勒·凡尔纳
And he loves Jules Verne, you know?
跟我一样
Just like me.
我们聊得很开心  安琪
I mean, we were... we were having a great time, Angie, you know?
我本以为他可以来家里
I-I thought he could come home, you know?
他可以和我们一起生活
He could live with us. But, uh...
我不知道
I don't know, I just... I...
而我说了一些让他爆发的话
I said something that set him off,
而我却无力挽回
and I-I could not reel him back in.
我
I...
在那之后我不停的在想
I kept thinking, after...
如果我们在小时候就知道对方
if-if we had known each other when I was growing up,
也许我能帮助他
maybe-maybe I could've helped,
也许他就不是现在这个样子了
maybe he wouldn't be where he is now.
你知道那是不可能的
You know that that is not true.
不可能吗
No?
我本来可以爱他的
I could have loved him.
现在爱他也来得及啊
You can do that now.
你还是可以爱他的
You can still love him.
我想说  这是你的钱
All I'm saying is that this is your money,
你努力工作挣的钱  不是我挣的
from your hard work, not mine.
提到钱的事  男人就变笨了
Men are so foolish when it comes to money.
所以才会战争四起
It's why we have so many wars.
你喜欢沾染着血汗的战利品
You like your loot covered in blood and sweat.
只有这样你才会高兴
It's the only way you can enjoy it.
所以怎样  我像是匈奴王阿提拉了吗
Okay, great. So, what? I'm Attila the Hun, now?
阿提拉: 在西欧被视为残暴及抢夺的象征
拜托  你就有一点儿像
I mean, come on. You're a little bit...
什么意思  有一点儿像匈奴王阿提拉
What do you mean, a little bit like Attila the Hun?
他在那儿  小甜甜
There he is. Sweets.
我跟那个与凯瑟琳·弗兰克
So I talked to the trainer
有染的谈过话
that Katherine Frank was sleeping with.
劳伦失踪时他出城了
He was out of town when Lauren disappeared.
现在都没回
He still is.
所以他不是同伙
So he's not an accomplice.
-她不是嫌疑人  -别这么快下结论
- And she's not a suspect. - Not so fast.
看这个
Check this out.
什么情况
What do we got here?
绑架勒索保险
Kidnapping and ransom insurance...
她给全家人都上了
She took out a kidnapping policy
绑架保险
on her whole family.
所以她绑架了劳伦
So... what? She kidnaps Lauren,
情况有变
things goes wrong,
她还是想拿到钱
she still tries to get the money...
布斯
Booth.
被害人的手机
The victim's phone
发的这些信息
sent those texts,
手机还在被害人家里
and the phone is still in the victim's house.
索要赎金的信息是劳伦的手机发送的
The ransom texts were sent from Lauren's phone.
手机还在房子里
It's still in the house.
确切位置是
Yeah, the east side
房子的东边
of the house, to be exact.
到了那儿给我打电话  布斯
Call me when you get there, Booth,
我告诉你怎么找到手机
and I'll tell you where to find it.
我需要手机里的
I need that phone to see
其他信息
the other information that it contains.
好  我们马上去
All right, we're on our way.
到了给你打电话
We'll call you when we get there.
我们到了  安琪拉
Okay, we're here, Angela.
他在干什么  史蒂文
What's he doing, Steven?
怎么了  布斯探员
What's going on, Agent Booth?
请别妨害公务
Please let me do my job.
我用反向911
I'm using Reverse 911
开机  仔细听
to turn on the phone, so listen for it.
骨头  听手机铃音
Okay, Bones, listen for a high-pitched squeal.
门厅那边  布斯
Down that hallway, Booth!
-找到没  -找到了  布斯
- Got it? - Got it, Booth!
这是你的健身器材吗
So is this your exercise equipment?
是的
Yes.
那是劳伦的手机
That's Lauren's phone.
我  我不知道
I-I didn't know
手机在那里
it was in there.
别用那种眼神看我
Don't look at me like that.
我们知道你和你的教练有染
So, we know that you and your trainer were having an affair.
根据你的婚前协议
All right, according to your prenup,
如果你出轨
if you have an affair, uh,
你丈夫会和你离婚
your husband gets a divorce
你一毛钱都分不到  是吧
and you don't get any money. Correct?
这怎么能表明我是嫌犯呢
And how does that make me a murder suspect?
拜托  别装傻
Come on. Seriously?
劳伦回家  看到你和教练发生关系
Lauren comes home and sees you having sex with the trainer,
如果她告诉她父亲
and if she told her dad,
你就完了
you'd end up living in the car.
但是如果你杀了劳伦
But if you could get rid of Lauren,
绑架保险就会生效
then the kidnapping policy would kick in...
保险是史蒂文买的
Steven bought that.
你签的字啊
The policy's in your name.
为了免税
For tax purposes.
-史蒂文总想把钱藏着  -你怎么做的
- Steven is always trying to hide money. - How'd you do it?
她怎么死的
How'd she die?
这也是你计划的一部分吗
Was that always part of your plan?
我跟劳伦可能处得不太好
I might have not gotten along with her,
但是绝不可能伤害她
but I could never hurt Lauren.
我认为你杀了她
I think you had to kill her,
因为不管怎样  保险都会生效
because the policy would kick in either way,
劳伦死了  就没有证人了
and with Lauren dead, there'd be no witness.
我一直很合作
I've tried to help.
现在我不合作了
But I'm done.
-我要找律师  -行
- I want my lawyer. - Good.
你确实需要个律师
'Cause you're gonna need one.
劳伦的手机被用来发送信息
So Lauren's phone was used to send the texts.
是她继母发的
And the stepmother sent them.
任何人都可能发
Well, it could have been anybody.
手机被设定自动开机
The phone was set to turn itself on,
发送信息  然后马上关机
send the text, and then immediately
所以我们无法进行追踪
turn itself off so we couldn't trace it.
对于凯瑟琳来说这太
That's way too tech-savvy
高科技了  我意思是
for Katherine. I mean, she's the only one
她是房子里唯一一个没有电脑的  对吧
in the house that didn't have a computer, right?
那些是什么
What are those?
是一排等待发送的信息
Oh, those are texts in a queue, waiting to be sent.
都被史蒂文·弗兰克的软件加密了
They're all encrypted with Steven Frank's software.
你可以直接联系他啊
So you could just call him.
这次他不打算合作了
Well, he's not gonna help this time.
他认为我们在对他妻子逼供
He thinks we're railroading his wife.
或者
Or...
他也与此事有关  凯瑟琳使他确信
he's involved because Katherine convinced him
劳伦妨碍了他们的婚姻
that Lauren was getting in the way of their new marriage.
你认为他和凯瑟琳合谋
Wait. You think that he and Katherine together...?
太可怕了
That's horrible.
我们面对的可是
I mean, we're dealing with murder
谋杀和绑架啊
and kidnapping.
通常这都是很可怕的
That's usually pretty horrible.
父亲和继母都说得通
The father and the stepmother make sense.
他们都住在那栋房子里
They were both in the house.
都能接触到手机
They had access to the phone...
他不合作
He's not cooperating.
听着  骨头  关于那笔钱
Listen, Bones, um... about the money...
别担心  布斯
Don't worry about it, Booth.
我会存进银行
I'll deposit the check.
不不  不是那个意思  是
No, no, no. It's not that. It's just...
你知道  如果那笔钱是我们的
You know, if the money is ours, together,
属于我们共同的财产
like, really ours together,
那我是不是有权决定怎么花
do I get a say in how it's spent?
当然
Of course.
那我想把那笔钱给哈金斯和安琪拉
Then I'd like to give the check to Hodgins and Angela.
给哈金斯的哥哥  他就能留在那里
To Hodgins' brother, so he can stay where he is.
听着  如果你不想要我这么做
Look, if you don't want me to...
当然可以
Of course.
我们一起给
We can do it together,
就像
like a...
你把派掉我裤子上了
You got pie on my pants.
你再买一件就行啦
You can afford another pair.
对不起  如果我之前在这里
I'm sorry, because if I was here,
我就会早些发现
I would have caught this earlier.
看  骨板和小管里面
Look, there was iron oxide
有氧化铁
caught in the osteons as well as canaliculi.
-是三氧化二铁  -铁锈
- It's-it's red oxide. - Rust.
用于移除她脚趾的工具生锈了
So whatever was used to remove her toe was rusty.
还有有机物
There was also organic particulates
我正在鉴别
I'm trying to I.D. Now.
我  我想有机物可能不够
I just... I don't think I have enough.
被切断的脚趾末端很脏
Well, the severed end of the toe is filthy,
应该够你鉴别的
so you should have more than enough there.
我去给你发现的东西做DNA测试
And I'll run DNA on whatever you find.
你用来啃掉尸体肌肉部分的那些
Any news from the beetles
甲虫有什么发现
that you used to deflesh the remains?
很快就有结果
Soon.
我只是
I just...
看望我哥回来之后
I-I couldn't grind them up
我还没能研磨它们
after I came back from seeing my brother.
-挺愚蠢的  我知道  -哈金斯博士
- It's so stupid, I know... -Uh, Dr. Hodgins,
-要费什先生帮你吗  -不用
- do you want Mr. Fisher to do it for you? - No.
不用  这是我的工作
No. They're mine.
马上给你结果
I'll have the results for you soon.
我知道我们在尺骨和C7上
I think I understand the saw marks
发现的锯痕是怎么回事了
we found on the ulna and the C7.
他们损害都不严重
They didn't do much damage.
所有锯痕都是她死后产生的
All marks are postmortem, made after she died.
我认为凶手确实想要肢解劳伦
I believe the killer did want
以便抛尸
to dismember Lauren to dispose of her body.
所以他毁了她的牙齿
That's why he destroyed her teeth.
让人没法鉴别她的身份
To obscure her identity.
只毁了部分牙齿  不是全部
But only some of her teeth. Barely enough.
他被干扰了
He was interrupted.
看这些犹豫的标记
Look at these hesitation marks.
-如果我们能找到干扰他的人  -不
- If we can find who interrupted him... - No.
锯痕开始和停止才是
Hesitation marks would show signs
犹豫的标记
of starting and stopping.
这些只是停止的标记
These simply stop.
她得了破伤风
She had tetanus.
我看到哈金斯博士发现的
When I saw the rust
伤口上的铁锈
Dr. Hodgins found in the wounds,
我检验了骨板
I tested the osteons.
破伤风不是死因
Tetanus wouldn't kill her.
不是  但是让她生病了
No, but it made her very sick.
是种有毒菌株
It was a virulent strain,
发作快  除了铁锈之外
fast-moving, because something else
她被别的病毒感染了
infected her in addition to the rust.
她可能出现了高热
She probably had a high fever,
高血压  痉挛之类的
blood pressure, spasms...
会让一个新手绑架犯手忙脚乱
That would freak out a first-time kidnapper.
我认为他本想帮她
I think he tried to help her.
看甲虫的检测结果
Look what the beetles gave us.
青霉素
Penicillin.
这量太大了
That is an enormous amount to give someone.
会引起癫痫  根据她的医疗记录
They'd have a seizure. According to her medical records,
她对青霉素过敏
she was allergic to penicillin.
这份量会杀死她
Then that amount would killed her.
但是她病了  给她青霉素的人
But she was sick, so whoever gave her
不是想杀她
the penicillin wasn't trying to kill her;
而是想救她
they wanted to save her.
我讨厌
Okay, I hate to be the one
觉得世界和谐美好  不过我宣布
in rose-colored glasses here, but I'm going to go on record:
这是场意外
This was an accident.
杀了劳伦人其实很爱她
Whoever killed Lauren loved her.
既不是刀也不是锯子
It wasn't a knife or a saw.
脚趾是被某种铁剪剪掉的
Some kind of iron clippers were used to sever the toe.
所以脚趾骨末端才会碎掉
Which is why the bone was crushed at the end.
园艺剪吗
Gardening shears?
不是  更小点  跟指甲剪差不多的
No, smaller. Almost like these nail clippers here.
你在组织上找到的
And the organic material
-有机物是什么  -是微量的
- you found on the tissue? - It was microscopic
排泄物  凯在验DNA
amounts of feces. Cam's running it for DNA.
像是某人卫生间里的钳子
Sounds like clippers from someone's bathroom.
我才不想看你的卫生间呢
Ew. I do not want to see your bathroom.
我有室友
I have roommates.
-还需要什么就跟我说  -行
- Let me know if you need anything else. - Yep.
哈金斯博士
Oh, Dr. Hodgins...
关于你哥哥的事
about your brother...
我没事  费什
I'm-I'm fine, Fisher.
你不可能没事
Well, that's not true.
听着  我在疯人院待过一段时间
Look, I've spent time at the loony bin.
我跟感激那段日子
And I was grateful for it.
因为人有时候就应该待在那里
Because sometimes it's the right place to be.
痛苦吗  当然了
Painful, sure.
但更让人痛苦的是某些人的眼光
But what's worse is when someone would look at you
好像你不应该在那里
like you shouldn't be there.
那让我觉得我做错了什么
Always felt like I'd done something wrong
而不仅仅是生病了
rather than just... having a disease, you know.
我知道这话听起来很怪
I know this sounds crazy,
但是你应该为他在那里感到高兴
but you got to be happy for him in there.
尤其是现在他找到了你
Especially now that he's found you.
相信我  他刚刚中了大奖
Trust me, he just won the lottery.
好吧  这些都是我的心里话
Okay, so that was all sincere,
但这么说话让我觉得有点恶心
but I'm feeling a little sick talking like that,
所以我走了
so I'm gonna go now.
我解密了发出的信息
I'm decrypting the texts that were sent.
进展缓慢的原因的是每条信息
It's slow because each one
使用了独立的密码
used a separate encryption.
我们已经看过这条了
Well, we've seen this one already.
没有全部看完
Not the whole thing.
原始照片使用了Hipstashotz滤镜
The original was run through a Hipstashotz filter
剪切掉了这部分
to crop this out.
这是张自拍照
It's a selfie.
对  劳伦在绑架前三周拍下这张照片
Yeah, Lauren took it three weeks before the kidnapping,
并在今天发出
but it was sent today.
她策划绑架自己  为什么
She staged her own kidnapping. Why?
因为遛狗的人说了
Because the dog walker said
她想逃离她的家
that she wanted to get away from her family.
她习惯了有钱人的生活
I mean, she's used to having money.
显然  她没有工作
Clearly, she doesn't work.
但是她还需要一个同伙
But she still had to have an accomplice.
她不能把自己埋了
She didn't bury herself.
凯拿到了伤口处粪便的DNA
Hey, Cam got the DNA results from the feces in the wound.
它属于一条狗  弗兰克家的狗
It's from a dog. The Franks' dog.
是那个遛狗的人  谢谢  哈金斯
It was the dog walker. Thanks, Hodgins. Thanks.
还有件事  哈金斯
Oh-oh, uh, one more thing, Hodgins.
关于你哥哥
Listen, about your brother...
-不  布斯  没事的  -听我说完
- No, Booth, it's okay. - Let me finish.
骨头和我  我们想给你们点钱
Bones and I, we'd like to give you guys some money.
帮你们解决你哥哥的事
To help you out with your brother
让他可以继续待在现在的地方
so he can stay where he is.
直到你们找到解决办法  行吗
Until you guys come up with a plan, all right?
你们简直太好了
Wow. That's-That's really kind of you.
这真是  太谢谢你们了
It is. It is. Thank you very much.
就是我  我不能拿这钱
Um, I just... I can't take it.
为什么
Why?
我打算去贷款
I'm gonna get a loan...
跟银行贷
from a bank.
就像我没做过的普通人一样
Like the normal person that I've never been.
但是我们的办法更实际啊
But this is more practical.
这不是实际不实际的问题
It's not about being practical.
这是承担责任的问题
It's about being responsible.
我觉得像自尊心的问题
Seems like pride.
我只是想让你俩知道
Listen, I just want you both to know
骨头和我会一直支持你们
that Bones and I are here for both of you
无论你们需要什么帮助
if you guys ever need anything.
谢谢
Thank you.
-谢谢  -不不  别过来
- Thanks. - No, no, no. Oh, no!
只是握个手不行吗
Whatever happened to handshakes, okay?
好了好了  够了
Okay, that's good. That's enough.
够了  你们继续
That's enough. Take care.
我要去抓那个遛狗的人了
I've got to go get the dog walker now, all right?
走吧
Let's go.
你想把她尸体切开  毁容
You tried to cut her up, destroy her face
这样我们就不会知道她是谁
so we wouldn't know who she was,
但是你没有坚持下来
but you couldn't go through with it.
因为你爱她
Because you loved her.
对吧  你说过你们
Isn't that right? I mean, you said that you...
你们曾经坐在她的阳台上  对吧
you used to sit on her deck, right?
你们是在那里策划这起绑架的吗
Is that where you planned the kidnapping?
我们检查了你的剪刀
We tested your clippers,
你用来给狗修毛的剪刀
the ones you use to groom the dogs.
劳伦的脚趾就是用它剪下来的
They were used to cut off Lauren's toe.
她自己剪的
She did that herself.
她说只有这样才能让她父亲相信
She said it was the only way to convince
她被人绑架了
her father she'd been kidnapped.
-计划就是这样  -计划
- That was the plan. - The plan?
这计划糟透了
But that was a pretty bad plan,
因为你犯了谋杀罪  伙计
because you're about to go down for murder, Buddy.
我不是杀人犯
I'm not a murderer.
她的脚趾感染了
Look, her toe got infected,
她不让我送她去医院
and she wouldn't let me take her to the hospital,
所以我去了我工作的兽医院
so I went to the vet's where I work,
拿了一些抗生素
and I took some antibiotics.
青霉素
Penicillin.
是的  我拿了最好的那种
Yeah, I took the best one.
她对青霉素过敏
She was allergic to penicillin.
我不知道  我发誓
I didn't know that. I swear.
我们就要
Look, we were gonna...
我们就要一起私奔了
we were gonna run away together.
不  她就要跟别人一起私奔了
No, she was gonna run away with someone else.
她设计你参与了这起绑架
She was setting you up for the kidnapping.
我们解密了她手机要发出的最后一条信息
We decrypted the last text her phone was going to send.
那是给警方的  告诉他们你的位置
It was to the police, telling them where to find you.
她说了她爱我
She said she loved me.
我跟她说我们不需要那笔钱
I told her we didn't need the money.
我有份不错的工作
You know, I have a good job.
我只是想帮她
I was trying to help her.
等等  我没听懂
Wait, wait. I-I don't understand.
罗兹伦博士打来电话说杰弗里不见了
Dr. Rozran called, said Jeffrey disappeared.
他觉得是杰弗里
He thinks that Jeffrey
听到了自己要转院的事
overheard he was being moved to another facility
受到了刺激
and that set him off.
那就让医生和工作人员们去找他
So let the doctor and his staff find him.
他们知道去哪里找
They have the experience.
但是罗兹伦说过他只去几个地方
Yeah, but Rozran said he only goes to a couple of places, so...
哈金斯
Hey, Hodgins...
安琪  你说过我可以现在开始爱他的
Hey, Angie, you said I had a chance to love him now, right?
我现在就在爱他
Well, that's what I'm doing.
有需要的话  医生会过去的
The doctor will be there if I need him.
你找到他了就给我打电话
Call me when you get him back.
敬我们的联名账户
To our joint account.
他们让我从世界日落和
They gave me a choice between sunsets around the world or...
辛普森一家里面选
the Simpsons, huh?
所以你想用这笔钱干啥
So what do you want to do with the money?
我知道"超级球"就要到了
I know the Superball is coming up
你不是一直想去嘛
and you've always wanted to go.
超级碗
"Super Bowl."
是超级碗  不是超级球
It's Super Bowl, not Superball.
现在去看比赛太晚了
Anyways, listen, it's too late in the game right now
机票啊  酒店什么的
for plane tickets and a hotel room.
会把支票上的钱花光的
It would cost the whole check.
我无所谓啊  你一直表现得这么好
That's fine with me. You've been a good man.
我其实  在考虑
Well, I was... I was thinking
一些别的事情  比如
about something else, about...
让这钱为我们服务
putting it to work for us.
-投资吗  -是的
- Uh, investing it. - Yes!
干得好啊  布斯
I'm impressed, Booth.
我找到了一个很好的项目
I came up with something really good.
"受伤老兵计划
"Wounded Warrior Project.
帮助伤者和他们的家庭"
Empowering the wounded and their families."
这个项目是为了资助
Yeah, it's a tough go after you've been injured, you know,
服役期间受伤还乡的军人
in the service and you come home.
也帮助他们的家人
For the families, too.
我觉得这是很好的投资  对吧
I think it's a good investment, right?
是的
Yes.
太好了
Yeah.
所以说你很会花钱啊  布斯
It turns out you're very good with your money, Booth.
干杯  谢谢  骨头
Cheers. Thanks, Bones.
杰弗里
Jeffrey?
Jeffrey.
我给你带了件外套
I brought you a coat.
不  不
No, no!
不  都是你
No! No, it was you!
你是那个想把我送走的人
You're the one that was gonna send me away!
听着  你误会了  好吗
Listen, it was a mix-up, okay?
我想带你回去
I want to bring you back.
你是政府的人
You're from the Federation.
你们创造出了这稳定的假象
You're the one that creates the static that-that-that...
我想带你回家
I'm going to take you back to your home.
你永远都不用离开那里
And you're never going to have to leave there.
-我发誓  -不
- I promise. - No.
-我绝不会相信一名特工  -说得对
- I will never trust an operative. - That's right.
说得对  你绝不要相信一名特工
That's right. You-You'd never trust an operative, okay?
但是你可以相信自己的弟弟
But you can trust your brother.
我是你的弟弟  杰弗里
I... I'm your brother, Jeffrey.
我是杰克·哈金斯
I'm Jack Hodgins.
你还记得妈妈爸爸吗
Hey, you-you remember Mom and Dad?
罗兹伦博士说你的房间里
Dr. Rozran said that you still have
还有一张他们的照片
a picture of them in your room.
看  我也有一张  看到了吗
Well, here, I got one, too. You see that?
就是他们
That's them.
中间的是我
And that's me.
我一直都不知道
Man, I never knew it,
但我想我这辈子都一直在找你
but I guess I've been looking for you my whole life.
为了让这照片圆满
To complete the picture.
我终于可以像你一样看穿静电了
I can finally see past the static, Jeffrey, like you.
让我带你回去吧
Let me bring you back.
我发誓你永远都不用离开家了
I promise you'll never have to leave your home.
永远
Never.
那是...
Is that...
你怎么这么了解《海底两万里》
how you know 20,000 Leagues so well?
他也读给你听了吗
Did he read it to you, too?
是啊  他给我读过
Yeah, he did.
每晚都读
Every night.
就像他以前给你读那样
Just like he must have to you.
1866年
"The year 1866
因一件不平常的事件闻名
was signalized by a remarkable incident."
一种神秘而令人费解的现象
"A mysterious and puzzling phenomenon
将令所有人难以忘怀
that surely no one has forgotten."
先不说那些
"Without going into the rumors that...
扰乱海滨居民
"...upset civilians in the seaports
和震惊世人  甚至是内陆的奇闻怪事
"and deranged the public mind, even far inland,
我们来说件让资深水手们提高警惕的事情
it must be said that professional seamen were especially alarmed."